[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of nightmare does Ed have at the end of the 1972 movie Deliverance?", "correct_answer": "A dead mans hand appears from the lake.", "incorrect_answers": ["He kills himself.", "His baby daughter tries to kill him.", "A deer is chasing him through the woods."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A turtles eggs are leathery and soft.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the nerd, portrayed by David Spade, say to the waitress at Pizza Hut in movie The Benchwarmers?", "correct_answer": "I like salad", "incorrect_answers": ["I am never coming here again", "This food is good", "Your hot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of animal is Old Yeller featured in the 1957 classic film Old Yeller?", "correct_answer": "Dog", "incorrect_answers": ["Panther", "Grizzly Bear", "Mountain Lion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country are the priciest emeralds in the world found?", "correct_answer": "Colombia", "incorrect_answers": ["Peru", "South Africa", "India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Garlic worsens which of these medical conditions?", "correct_answer": "Stomach ulcer", "incorrect_answers": ["Diabetes", "Intestinal worms", "Hypertension"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 1955 movie won four Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Marty", "incorrect_answers": ["Forrest Gump", "Crash", "The Wizard of Oz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Turtles are cold-blooded, meaning their internal temperature varies according to their outside environment.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest number mentioned in the Bible?", "correct_answer": "1,000,000", "incorrect_answers": ["30,000", "400,000", "100,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "R2D2 and C3PO are part of what saga?", "correct_answer": "Star Wars", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Blade Runner", "Star Trek"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which line contains only names of people who have or had AIDS?", "correct_answer": "Magic Johnson, Isaac Asimov", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim Morrison, Bob Marley", "Tony Richardson, Kurt Cobain", "Freddie Mercury, Jimi Hendrix"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The sound of what musical instrument does the call of the Macaroni Penguin resemble?", "correct_answer": "Trumpet", "incorrect_answers": ["Saxophone", "Flute", "Ocarina"]}]